const STORE = [
    {
    question: "Who is the franchise leader in rushing yards?",
    answer: [ 
        'Marshawn Lynch',
        'Shaun Alexander',
        'Curt Warner',
        'Chris Warren'
    ],
    correctAnswer: "Shawn Alexander"
    },
    {
    question: "Who is the franchise leader in touchdown passes?",
    answer: [
        'Russell Wilson',
        'Matt Hasselbeck',
        'Dave Krieg',
        'Charlie Whitehurst'
    ],
    correctAnswer: 'Russell Wilson'
    },
    {
    question: "What year did the franchise begin?",
    answer: [
        '1970',
        '2012',
        '1085',
        '1976'
    ],
    correctAnswer: '1976'
    },
    {
    question: 'What conference did the team originally start in?',
    answer: [
        'AFC',
        'NFC',
        'XFL',
        'CFL'
    ],
    correctAnswer: 'NFC'
    },
    {
    question: "How many Super Bowls have the Seahawks been to?",
    answer: [
        '1',
        '3',
        '5',
        '10'
    ],
    correctAnswer: '3'
    },
    {
    question: 'Who is the franchise leader in interceptions?',
    answer: [
        'Dave Brown',
        'Richard Sherman',
        'Eugene Robinson',
        'Earl Thomas'
    ],
    correctAnswer: 'Dave Brown'
    },
    {
    question: 'What season did the Seahawks win the Superbowl?',
    answer: [
        '05-06',
        '13-14',
        '14-15',
        '83-84'
    ],
    correctAnswer: '13-14'
    },
    {
    question: 'Who is the franchise leader in recieving yards?',
    answer: [
        'Doug Baldwin',
        'Steve Largent',
        'Brian Blades',
        'Joey Galloway'
    ],
    correctAnswer: 'Steve Largent'
    },
    {
    question: 'Who is the franchise leader in passing yards?',
    answer: [
        'Russell Wilson',
        'Dave Krieg',
        'Matt Hasselbeck',
        'Jim Zorn'
    ],
    correctAnswer: 'Matt Hasselbeck'
    },
    {
    question: 'Who is the winningest coach in franchise history?',
    answer: [
        'Mike Holmgren',
        'Chuck Knox',
        'Pete Carroll',
        'Jack Patera'
    ],
    correctAnswer: 'Pete Carroll'
    }
]


